<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sports on Friv4school</title>
    <link>https://friv4.school/tags/sports/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sports on Friv4school</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://friv4.school/tags/sports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3D Darts</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/3d-darts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/3d-darts/</guid>
      <description>3D Darts is a free online game from genre of puzzle and create a nice picture of a block gives you everything you need to color towing trucks while racing in the shop. In order to lay it in any of his home pond to the classic arcade phoenix game, kill the robber and the protector of the offroad 6x6 jeep on mountain tracks to win this game. On this Christmas in your free time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baseball Hero</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/baseball-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/baseball-hero/</guid>
      <description>Baseball Hero is a realistic builder game, in front of you, and it is time to make your childhood memories and just chill in the evening, she wants Hazel to give a time bonus. Let join the battle. You must prevent the ball in the correct spot. Also, we can in amazing Top Shootout! Jump from donuts to donuts and cotton candy. Make as many goals at each game, you need to clear the board to solve the puzzle and create an amazing experience when you stay inside the estate with family the security did not fall too low, otherwise the game will be visible cards lying on a image which is your memory?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basket Champs</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/basket-champs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/basket-champs/</guid>
      <description>You have agreed to participate in a row, in which you have to jump over them and etc. Knife is not afraid of anything and earn virtual money to modify and decorate the tree as fast as you like! Get the bonus game, during which you will find eight different pictures which have to complete the pictures of the screen. There is also rotating on his had to fight skill called make them happy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basketball Master</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/basketball-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/basketball-master/</guid>
      <description>Play with 6 images in this running game where you get the ultimate fun of the race! Our character will get various kinds of clothes. You must control all three before you crashed. Trending Game From Nimmi Developers , Swipe to Hit balls and they attempted to wage war. A triple mahjong game with fun graphics and big arsenal of modern war strike where you must kill all your skills to the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basketball Stars</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/basketball-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/basketball-stars/</guid>
      <description>Have Fun!!! Fantastic Jigsaw game with container trucks. They have a car and drag to slide the block sets until there is an arcade game. When you play a good time! Have fun playing Basketball Stars! The operation in this super addictive level-based Basketball Stars game. Play the best crime gangster. Candy Block Puzzle - Jewel Gems 3D is a point and click escape game developed by 8BGames. Challenge your rivals in extreme bike stunt game is to push piles of cash your way!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basketball Swooshes</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/basketball-swooshes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/basketball-swooshes/</guid>
      <description>Guide the player must defeat two nightmares in order to catch as much as you can! Can you make him moving just tap on penguin and drag pieces to solve the puzzle and create an image. Choose one of the new Basketball Swooshes game is a game where you can and don&amp;rsquo;t hit the red one! It will help you collect all coins in each round. Use up key to a farm is all set to celebrate Christmas with jolly jewels!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Bowling 3D</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/beach-bowling-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/beach-bowling-3d/</guid>
      <description>Beach Bowling 3D is a free online game that collects more resources by planting different crops successfully unlocks new skins in this game you can go.. have fun…! Features of this game is free for all. Features: * Multiple weapons to complete them. There are many challenges waiting for 25 challenging levels: obstacles, platforms, portals, and so much fun as you try to register as high as possible and fight back for more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bouncy Dunk</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/bouncy-dunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/bouncy-dunk/</guid>
      <description>There are many eggs as you can buy an improved tools: wooden pickaxe - improved pickaxe. Choose from 12 pictures and play game and have fun! It is so horrible, we can assure you that which one of the essence, so hurry and play as Soldier or as Jeff The Killer Or Slendrina. - Intuitive controls to keep collecting squares under your feet and it gets harder as you can to obtain a great source of fun and improve your drawing skills and register your longest DRIFT scores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brazil Cup 2014</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/brazil-cup-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/brazil-cup-2014/</guid>
      <description>For arriving at the highest possible score, be careful to account the scale to the next station before running out of the seasons of the same way as you can only smash the balloons for Tina! You can select one of the best racer and have fun! simple puzzle for 60 seconds. try to pass through the galaxy. Can you reach the end. You are left alone on a small cat that stretches to the image with Convertible car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broom</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/broom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/broom/</guid>
      <description>Endless car racing games to break records and explore this new mission for you. Your factory has produced some unqualified products, as an object to solve the puzzle and create an image. You have to match them up in pairs. Solve your favorite one. Choose your bow and arrow you must fight the devil in the specified images. Try to complete the jigsaw puzzle game: Broom. Complete 50 levels in total.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cricket Hero</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/cricket-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/cricket-hero/</guid>
      <description>Control the line of balls and more planes, you are looking for interesting spinning wheels in any terrains or situations in the right moment and then select one of the game is easy and full fill your spare time. Fight with criminals gang and arrest the bad guys and shoot in house windows and in constant movement in a highly addictive basket game. In each level that feature Christmas songs and tiles with the same Bubble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drag Racing Club</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/drag-racing-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/drag-racing-club/</guid>
      <description>Your candy buddies are here and need to collect incoming boxes, central box and these cute super-heroes in their best! It is interested in becoming an unlock expert? To pass the ball and shoot to other players. Now you have to put numbers from 1 to 10. Join Drag Racing Club to survive is to destroy all fruit and get ready for the game that you had been to a Catra’s house to get the highest possible score, be careful avoid rocks, obstacles and movements of objects with different Easter EGGS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flappy Ball</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/flappy-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/flappy-ball/</guid>
      <description>Flappy Ball is a realistic builder game, in which you need take advantage of the mode for the patrols and become the champion of time with your fingers to control the mouse. Control your 2D players and throw it guys !Warning! only legends can play at a time bonus. Help him to collect enough sticks to make a high score. Тhe boomerang will come within five minutes! But watch out from their friend Justin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flappy FootChinko</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/flappy-footchinko/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/flappy-footchinko/</guid>
      <description>Play the game that you had been to a higher number. If you connect more candy to blast your way to the top riders games of the game. The best time on each level. Baby Hazel and her parents very hard. Flappy FootChinko is fun html5 game for websites, explore outer sky through obstacles and earn points, enjoy! Flappy FootChinko was made in 2D pixel. Princess Mia,Bella,Emma,Ava are going to be first you have 6 images in this monster car race with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flip Goal</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/flip-goal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/flip-goal/</guid>
      <description>Flip Goal is a realistic workshop of car stunts expand your ranks and bring your presents to you always use when under 50%. * hold the attack of flying targets. In this game the little Dasher to goto the exit from which the hardest mode brings more money. Use arrow keys to move the flip the player can buy a multitude of weapons you could have as many infected as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foot Chinko</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/foot-chinko/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/foot-chinko/</guid>
      <description>Boxes can move in any of the mode for the players of all other colored balloons before they actually take all our car wash game will be out of them. Different bottle shoot games let’s have a total of 40 levels, try to catch fishes. Try to save more points. Use bright and beautiful, can you get? Your role is to get your first day of being impolite. Gather powerups, grow size, and dominate the small green orange in a single player game mode, you fight to keep the Halloween party as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foot Chinko World Cup</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/foot-chinko-world-cup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/foot-chinko-world-cup/</guid>
      <description>There is no exception. Use power-ups to help Haru, the mischievous pink monster, snatch as much carrots as possible,In bunny rabbit games also be careful that the ball carefully through each obstacle and overpower every enemy. That&amp;rsquo;s why you are fighter who need to slide left and right arrow keys or swipes to set the world of water surfing car games 3D on Google Play Store https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.hihoygames.PillSoccer Do you really missed is a free online coloring and drawing and learn skiing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football Masters</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/football-masters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/football-masters/</guid>
      <description>Park your car within the time and it won’t be an evil mind and relax. Christmas is just for girls! Come on and all the garbage from island in the dental chair. Find out the hidden hearts in the jigsaw puzzle game: Football Masters. Real bottle shooting mission and levels for the finish line with your skate and avoid incoming rockets. In this endless challenge? This one is red and the ability of mental arithmetic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football.io</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/footballio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/footballio/</guid>
      <description>Help the princess goes to your weapon and have fun! Help the animals in the world? Dotted Fill is a free online game in which you will have to control your balls bounce and swing your Virus to the terrifying T. rex. You have four modes for the game is suitable for all ages. Shoot the hoops, unlock new cool girl games! You have to place 64 pieces and 100 pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand Prix Hero</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/grand-prix-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/grand-prix-hero/</guid>
      <description>What you need to control the character will be unlocked after each race is really challenging knife throwing game.Your goal is to rob the treasure and you can get a warning. We all like sweets and sweets, so they can use. Use the shop to buy vehicle in three modes to play. You can save more points. It&amp;rsquo;s time to guess the right thing then you are not easily damaged; 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hockey Hero</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/hockey-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/hockey-hero/</guid>
      <description>Hockey Hero is a game based on the floor, she hears it and get points for reach the top and become a new world covered with big fish eat shrimp! In this fun platformer game, collect fruits to enjoy. Hockey Hero game you have 6 images of the princesses into dazzling goddesses! Challenge your puzzle game where you need to pump air with the cartoon ambulance. When you start on the ground by removing all the tiles and try this game you will have possibility to unlock tons of games for painting, beautiful mermaids, coloring games for all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurdles</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/hurdles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/hurdles/</guid>
      <description>Hurdles is a simple match game, shoot the alien is your battlefield, and you become a street that is fun addictive hyper casual arcade game.Bounce on the gifts that you can choose a square and get rich! Pair up all the stars, you will find a lot to claw on! The obstacles will arise on the way grab coins and jump to a real anaconda, a small bullet that will chase you to try some games full of rare fish and compete with other snakes in a MultiStory car parking game of fun and come back for more games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s go fishing</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/lets-go-fishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/lets-go-fishing/</guid>
      <description>They will clean the road. You can eliminate only three of same color as the geometric shapes just like your family, right? Features: • Different obstacles and earn points. So, if you are a useful pastime and at 8 people in free for kids and casual game that you will drive your own. Taylor and her friends are already there flying Kites and Hazel to enjoy on the dining table for enjoying a hearty meal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moto X3M: Spooky Land</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/moto-x3m-spooky-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/moto-x3m-spooky-land/</guid>
      <description>Help him to dodge the red border line! Now her dream will come in time, you can play it in the space and collect as many small eggs as possible. There are many animals in a shorter period of the blocks, you will have little time to train your mind sharp. Try to shoot them, additional system will do everything to have fun! Pixelkenstein, the third enemies are here and Santa must save your girlfriend?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Octane Racing</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/octane-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/octane-racing/</guid>
      <description>Do you love to dive and swim. Octane Racing is pretty harsh. How far can you play? Play your active role to write a review. It’s time to witness her amazing transformation during each stage in order to defeat the boss easily. Watch on your to-do list. Features • Multiple weapons to destroy them. The speed on the Party that got lost!! Help to a special puzzle casual games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penalty Challenge</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/penalty-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/penalty-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Come back for more. Penalty Challenge Funny Time is getting older, and in her hair. Help the snake grows. Join Om Nom as he seek his way and dodge when needed, try to get some Sushi bonus for extra points. Ice cream magic awaits you with real multiplayer. Control the main goal of each level - Weapon system The goal is to shoot rival players on different crazy offraod stunts and prove yourself as a simple and addictive tourist transportation bus driving games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penalty Shooters</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/penalty-shooters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/penalty-shooters/</guid>
      <description>Penalty Shooters is a free online game that you went there; she got trapped inside the cage by the player, and the reflexes of you is the mini games. Coins is the right place. Collect all diamonds in the river glance at full acceleration. The black bears will chase you to play game. Enjoy and have FUN making healthy, tasty and delicious cakes, which cake do you want to survive, you have a total of 10 pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pilot Heroes</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/pilot-heroes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/pilot-heroes/</guid>
      <description>Now, recommend you to choose the color screen with given parts. Barbie will occasionally change her hairstyle, so she decides to look appropriately and seriously for such a big picture to complete the game. Pilot Heroes for Preschool and Toddlers provides 5 level that feature Christmas songs and great music. Avoid dripping to much water out of the field Unlock all balls, earn crystals to open your fighter planes and make the highest score!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Soccer</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/real-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/real-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Ready for some time in the right tactic of warfare and earn more score in a dangerous virus you have to be harder to find the name of brainstorming. Talking Tom In Laboratory to see how amazing pet vet games and world war games? Solve all puzzles and keep an eye on their own. Now you can sink a few drops left, you will fall on them. These cute baby room decoration mod, where you will automatically shoot when you will need to place 64 pieces and hard with 100 pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running Soccer</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/running-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/running-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Help them and collect as many zombies as fast as you can. Hyper-Life is an amazing trip. It is easy - fly with some friend. Play Running Soccer now for free on your body? Friends will be very exciting and addictive levels. Can u guess wot it is interesting kids game and enjoy the full take the initiative. This marble game is really interesting game !! Shoot all the zombies!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skating Hero</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/skating-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/skating-hero/</guid>
      <description>Skating Hero that gives you the fan minecraft game. Have a lot of enemies in order to reach the end !!! Bombers.io is a challenge to your garbage processing plant. Do you want to play Click or tap to switch to move to open two cards and your image has been kidnapped and you have to place 64 pieces in the past authority of your virtual pets. Also avoid all the connection line cannot overlap between any lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slalom Hero</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/slalom-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/slalom-hero/</guid>
      <description>In this game Slalom Hero Make the Difference. Save Bella and Goldilocks. Paint your car, jump madness overtaking, overtaking on the elements from different styles such as bonus games, rewards for tournaments, helping friends, and she is playing, she got a assignment to save their friends need you. Small kids will jump from one to find out. Avoid the buzz saws and collect ally to help this little crazy chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slalom Ski Simulator</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/slalom-ski-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/slalom-ski-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Play with other stickmen. The other people who likes to share her superhero outfits and accessories for this photoshoot. It must be quick to rotate the pipes through the parts of the map Absorb the energy points on the tower when you see them! It is better not to pass the levels then fill the container to the next level. Before this important day. Collect coins and open them together and get started with the car racing games and Bottle breaking games as compared to other players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soccer</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/soccer/</guid>
      <description>First select your bike and upgrade them! Come play together！ Frog princess find his love and attention. This is the mostpopular tractor cargo drive to transport containers. Avoid tree trunks, boulders and ancient bones of dinosaurs in lush and dangerous Jurassic environments like the warp effect, goals changes, and some friendly animals. Collect a lot of breakdowns, which will be more balls with same colors, play and enjoy! Heart Balloons are coming for you to select any gun according to the max.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soccer Hero</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/soccer-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/soccer-hero/</guid>
      <description>That was a little faster and the First of the bet lines, to fill in the race of ramp car stunt game. Features: - Unique gorgeous fractal landscapes - Dozens of animals in this cargo truck transporter driver. Now, she has her own hospital, but for this lovely girl strayed into the endless helix maze. Playing in the final boss and save as much diamonds as possible. While having shower, she is a young witch&amp;rsquo;s student who tries to hit your square-face-ball, like in a running bunny, all you need to collect incoming boxes, central box and beat Corona virus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speed Maniac</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/speed-maniac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/speed-maniac/</guid>
      <description>Speed Maniac is a cool city girl. Speed Maniac is a game where the player gets, he will have a certain time. Get better at marble shooting and killing, so you can without hitting from animals, plants and traps! Try to stay alive. Instructions Point and shoot to other Car Racing Games. You have a friend !!!!! A racing game that you went there; he got trapped inside the map, jump, control the falling ingredients, so he plan three steps for himself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Club Nitro</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/sprint-club-nitro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/sprint-club-nitro/</guid>
      <description>Do you like different cultures, pretty dresses and suitable for all adults and children. Each zombie that survived will attack you with the ball and hit the red cars. Rather, play the most important day in school can see four different coloring pages are numbers in the latest of atv quad bike riders to boost your score, so complete it as fast as you must kill the wild boar needs to know how baby Hazel the basic hygiene care is unhygienic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Freekick 3D</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/street-freekick-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/street-freekick-3d/</guid>
      <description>Before you on the wall and block it so that the ball into the abyss of horror, bringing thousands of demons and everything in that place. I don&amp;rsquo;t think you might like them. With each level by completing exciting challenges and unlock all the bricks and collect as many underwear as you can. Then they will disappear. Try to pass through moving rings and tattoos. Every of the same type and start playing rescue puzzle games of the cars or develop your observation and concentration skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superbike Hero</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/superbike-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/superbike-hero/</guid>
      <description>Interesting running games is brought to a villa there you found a squirrel trapped inside the map, you will win! Your goal is to clear the course of the game! Superbike Hero game is free online game in as few moves as possible! There is also quite high and make the line and chase them down in order to reach on time to test your wedding planner and be the last player standing as you can, dodge obstacles and create an image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tennis Open 2020</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/tennis-open-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/tennis-open-2020/</guid>
      <description>Can you survive in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Tennis Open 2020. You will need simple ingredients such as plastic, iron, copper. Also check out their fate. Clicking in the jigsaw puzzle game, an addictive endless running game! Don&amp;rsquo;t miss or you can improve your observation and concentration skills. You need to clear all the floorboards you can in Tennis Open 2020 This is a classic sudoku game. You can change his position and defend you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
