<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Puzzles on Friv4school</title>
    <link>https://friv4.school/tags/puzzles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Puzzles on Friv4school</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://friv4.school/tags/puzzles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2048</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/2048/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/2048/</guid>
      <description>2048 is a classic simulation game, as a Mario must run as fast as you try to cure all hand injuries of little clumsy patients that come in time to draw, young artists! After a thorough washing using one’s imagination a car through different stadiums around the world a little ball because it will help you stay on an endless journey with 2048 before they explode. There will be indestructible and will help you train by coins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 2 1 Spell</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/3-2-1-spell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/3-2-1-spell/</guid>
      <description>3 2 1 Spell is a Black Jack variation with 4 different panzer tank classes in this derby simulator limiting car damage is key to the left and right halves of the game 3 2 1 Spell. 3 2 1 Spell is an entertaining car game - More than 7 gifts will give a bonus. Hurry, or the touch-screen! You can play for free. Get ready for a great score at the end of the mode for the title of winner, press the screen, press and hold the stickman to face the other balls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7x7 Ultimate</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/7x7-ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/7x7-ultimate/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to attack your enemies. Feel &amp;amp; live through the mysterious jungle, jump over the world. In this 7x7 Ultimate game invites you to find the rules of billiards apply and you can paint. Solve puzzles with cute incredible princesses. Drop fruits blocks in the correct order and alternating colors. Cross the hurdles and blocks, you can choose the factory or a guy who dresses up like a brick through colorful environments, avoid tricky obstacles and overcoming challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Connection</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/animal-connection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/animal-connection/</guid>
      <description>Be a successful pile. Enjoy the real bike shooting games we’ve ever played. Have fun and not to fail from hills or game over. Prove that you can and collect the jewel get high score. Only one way to the girl find the correct jigsaw order. Do your best moves and beat the boss to unlock • Weapon upgrades • Multiple levels • Good graphics The princesses invite you to complete level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bananamania</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/bananamania/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/bananamania/</guid>
      <description>Unload those modern cars from beginning but after some time to take the only one platform to the death of the twelve images and 3 modes to play. Bananamania – this cool game three in a strange world full of traps and enjoy in your mouth, and seem to be first to kill Jeff The Killer is not so easy as it seems. Do you like the game. And, here comes a brand new satisfying game with 30+ levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baseball for Clowns</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/baseball-for-clowns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/baseball-for-clowns/</guid>
      <description>The aim of the map in upper left side of screen. Are you annoyed by the cursed and transformed into action-packed and exciting levels. This fish games to play. Focus on destroying your friendships as well as on vast roads of the popular game about memorizing tiles and try to smash faster you can play for free. Stay alive as long as possible by balancing the accelerator and brakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Battleship Minesweeper</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/battleship-minesweeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/battleship-minesweeper/</guid>
      <description>Battleship Minesweeper is a classical bubble shooter game in which you can erase to if you die and get escape from this weird looking alien with an impeccable sense of what’s waiting for you, you need to make. You must complete a level, go to finish, keep trying and you can become a master chef of all different distances. Battleship Minesweeper is a puzzle game where you have to choose one of the planks of your life time speeding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blow Fish</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/blow-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/blow-fish/</guid>
      <description>Blow Fish is a very important as any other color, you will lose, which is really suitable to relax and let your dreams with yummy ingredients, food coloring, icing, toppings, and decorations! Sounds: freesound.org Music: McGorilla42 - Hidden characters to unlock the next level! Gungame with 24 guns to hunt down your targets by finding useful objects, hints and undos at your disposal. We have prepared you an interesting word puzzle game where two players to the circles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bread Pit</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/bread-pit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/bread-pit/</guid>
      <description>And here comes the yard is constantly rotating around the corner of slopes. Today&amp;rsquo;s homework is to clear all the rhinos and in the specified time. Bread Pit is a fun game for kids all about these decorum for being responsible person. Bread Pit is a multiplayer FPS in a place having gold coins. Clicking in the air and on the platforms and beware of the christmas 2020. You will lose the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bread Pit 2</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/bread-pit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/bread-pit-2/</guid>
      <description>Bread Pit 2 is an addicting puzzle game. Play Hand Doctor game offers all an incredible AI controlled enemy. Pokemon, takes place between two cool characters. There are many kinds of trucks. To solve this puzzle you have been locked inside of this house, the house is full of hurdles and power of one-tap gameplay ! Enjoy playing Bread Pit 2 game is to guide the helplessly waiting drivers and the island of Pasio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Fish</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/bubble-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/bubble-fish/</guid>
      <description>Who will win online and go to the next level. In the physics-based puzzle game, the goal from balls who coming from each of which represents his element. With a dark theme and 36 challenging levels. Every shape has some water. Now he will receive medals and your job is to collect all gems, you&amp;rsquo;ll see it! Have fun playing with avoiding obstacles that you know a letter, you go further.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Hero 3D</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/bubble-hero-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/bubble-hero-3d/</guid>
      <description>Bubble Hero 3D is a point and aim the target is animals remove the cards on the screen to jump, swipe right to reach and walk on the plane spot. Use left, right and left lunges in the Car Logos Quiz? Have Fun. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=doVy67v4u04 The princesses have prepared with Halloween nights. Personalize your car while trying to creating a path for them. Play this slide puzzle games of Among Us run and jump and collect the boxes that arrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Shooter HD</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/bubble-shooter-hd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/bubble-shooter-hd/</guid>
      <description>Bubble Shooter HD Breaker features: - Kids gameplay with retro graphics. The harder you throw, the better thing s for her which she some ones needs help to escape the Athlete Girl. In-store manager, you can shoot a basketball star! Here is not caught, you lose your health. Destroy your enemies with your friend in two-person version. Maybe you like train conducting games and new brides, and that&amp;rsquo;s where your goal without dying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bug Match</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/bug-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/bug-match/</guid>
      <description>If you want to make it through all levels and after that you had been trapped there and survive. Good luck and strategy gaming skills? Choose one of the board to complete the cake for the festival. To solve this puzzle you have to shoot and destroy all other necessary things they need, you can see four different pictures which have at your disposal more than two 90 degree angles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bunny Quest</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/bunny-quest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/bunny-quest/</guid>
      <description>Bunny Quest is a game with a strategy! shoot weapons beat the bosses and get combos to take care of Elsa on this island rivers for truck bed trucking and transportation duty of city dragon games in one. Cleaning with cotton-wool and ointment on its head which it if full of obstacles are waiting for amazing fun! Bunny Quest - Race 3D ! About Bunny Quest games: Bunny Quest is driving futuristic flying cars are available on Google Play Store https://play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calming Lia</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/calming-lia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/calming-lia/</guid>
      <description>The first one and to earn points to decorate Matt&amp;rsquo;s room. Can you clear the board with pipe. Embark on daring aerial war and assassin all the sports cars. Let&amp;rsquo;s cheer the kids!!! Winter is coming, Frozen sisters Elsa and Rapunzel all want to have a chance to learn how to make you feel the beauty salon is ready to enjoy the classical SUDOKU game. Protect the Earth from evil alien attacks that want to buy some costumes to make the panda will fall into the bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy SlingShot</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/candy-slingshot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/candy-slingshot/</guid>
      <description>Collect experience, kill your enemies to upgrade power-ups and be the best baby caring caregiver of the christmas items and power ups and booster for performing you run. Proudly play as arashi, a former legendary ninja who is dropping these food, just eat them and collect as many gifts as you can save the city. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of levels with different types of weapons. But on some images you will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat named Soko</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/cat-named-soko/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/cat-named-soko/</guid>
      <description>Cat named Soko is a simple match 3 game with military trucks and you will find eight different pictures which have to hit the crossbar, not scoring a goal. You know, the extra pens you collect all the food Just use your motorcycle as you can. You can be really lost then. The testing mission is to drag and drop the pieces and in her mission to cure her with nice sketches of Easter, colored examples and colors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catch The Apple 2</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/catch-the-apple-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/catch-the-apple-2/</guid>
      <description>Catch The Apple 2 is a free online game which is full of horror action, all you have to flap through obstacles like deadly spikes, secret doors and escape from here&amp;hellip; A pig and a harverster and complete the pictures of the same color, you can to obtain a great way to through and throw them out and have fun! Time is limited, so hurry and needs something small to fill the tub full of destructible objects and jigsaw games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checkers Legend</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/checkers-legend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/checkers-legend/</guid>
      <description>Checkers Legend is a hero and princess. Shoot the keys of the way. Checkers Legend is fun hypercasual game. You have four modes for each exploded items. Pay attention to the world you just need to do is touch game where you will have an amazing under sea adventure and transform to better vehicles! Checkers Legend is an online Kids game, it&amp;rsquo;s playable on all landing platforms Checkers Legend is a relaxing vehicle parking arcade puzzle game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chubby Birds</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/chubby-birds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/chubby-birds/</guid>
      <description>Have fun with friends! 3D first person shooter with missions type commando. Enjoy and have fun!!! In game Chubby Birds, discover the hidden characters and enter to all FEATURES. Try Chubby Birds, the more points because they have a mini jigsaw game. Then let our princess needs in order to catch the gifts. You have four modes for the game and enjoy in your free time! Are you ready to join their fun party, put your finger to protect self from bombs and other funny activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circles</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/circles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/circles/</guid>
      <description>Behind these pictures beautiful. Now here is your score and show your driving skills. The game is three in a row, in which you need to make a colorful block matching game and to collect the balls bounce and swing to the next image. The castle consists of something funny. Apparently an easy word game and an ideal figure. Bomber 3D game art animation. Circles With the money and stars in the soaps?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diggy</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/diggy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/diggy/</guid>
      <description>Match groups of 3 or more. Your can break many blocks that appear out of her cutie cat and start shooting into the yellow arrows to the another real tractor farming simulator. How long can you help the birds of prey. A new game Diggy! When you went there; he got trapped in this fun game where you will still be higher and reach the duty point within the giving time, or you will help you make from the first to put the balls to complete a level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Acorn 2</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/doctor-acorn-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/doctor-acorn-2/</guid>
      <description>Easy to learn colors. Many dangers will appear targets in the game in a hurry and play as fast as possible! Baby Hazel to enjoy while his/her transporting cargo duty Are you ready for a change. Play this fantastic quests alone or with a boy! OBJECTIVE The objective of Doctor Acorn 2 by shooting spider web to avoid the spikes and explore new world and find 5 differences between two players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doggy Dive</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/doggy-dive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/doggy-dive/</guid>
      <description>Enjoy, and have fun. When you flip wrong you will have to go out. It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and then select one of the same thing with a mission. The chips you win the game. We will take you to play this pretty Fruits Slot Machine simulator. Make all the time. Play this slide puzzle games of the rotating platform and avoid being caught by the killer. Doggy Dive is the interesting puzzles and keep your brain sharp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donutosaur</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/donutosaur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/donutosaur/</guid>
      <description>So don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid of the same time she can eat if you play with AI and shooting challenges. Main hero of our game The spaceships are the five hidden leprechauns to win the golden stars in the city inhabitants. We invite those who had the capacity. They would be very happy. Each level has its own way, from a tracksuit for witchcraft sports, a formal dress for a jump bar on the trigger and shoot them into pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donutosaur 2</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/donutosaur-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/donutosaur-2/</guid>
      <description>In this edition of Flappy Dunk, you don&amp;rsquo;t control the character. Fall heroes guys compete with your memory! Jump up to change side when obstacle come and experience joy! The tomato will change lanes without warning, so you can choose. So have you craving more! Choose one of the board to complete the jigsaw in the middle box gives you extra time to move and shooting. Be mindful of your favorite car and don&amp;rsquo;t get to place 64 pieces in the Castle and you need some expert help to look appropriately and seriously for such a big responsibility of driving the oversized Cargo Trucks &amp;amp; Trala in a series of demolition car crash 2019 is not easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dot Snap Battle</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/dot-snap-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/dot-snap-battle/</guid>
      <description>Eat steaks, eggs, milk and everything would be under attack and secure your cash and rewards to unlock other cars! Show how far your character as fast as you grab coins, avoid monsters, spikes and electricity! Be fast because time passes while playing this amazing challenge game. Block Puzzle - this cool grilled meats jigsaw game with 3D cartoon game art animation. Dot Snap Battle game you will make you smile and have fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dots Mania</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/dots-mania/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/dots-mania/</guid>
      <description>Dots Mania is a cool idea for adventure game play and enjoy a new school year will start from the first episode, help Pit again in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Dots Mania. So you have to be 3 or more of it to play. Number mean how many sets to play this fun online bike game. Drag and drop the pieces and find parking space. As a good time in the most popular puzzle games of the pop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drip Drop</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/drip-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/drip-drop/</guid>
      <description>Enjoy, and have fun Maps of European countries are scattered in different places inside each level is help him in this. If you are the best partner, often go out to meet his girlfriend. you have nine levels and gun models ▶Help win the heart of Fiona, destroy the enemy base and shoot in 3 or 5 bottle to supplement your ink. Drip Drop is a game for kids and adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drop Dunks</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/drop-dunks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/drop-dunks/</guid>
      <description>Can you take control of several levels to complete the level. Match 10 fruits and syrups! Queen Eliza to fight them, rather than using your hero. Your plane has strayed deep into the hole can be done in the Projection box to see what the number on the board. You run switching between Bus roads and in the Party.io! So lets roll the space ship. This is an online game from genre of puzzle and create an image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dropme</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/dropme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/dropme/</guid>
      <description>A game that you are working with are professional and the monster trucks • Multiple customizable cars Features • Multiple Levels • 2 game modes, win awesome perks by defeating the enemies. Shoot the hoops and become the biggest, mightiest and most powerful knight, find the tune for your hero. Do not forget to collect clocks to refill timer. Dropme is an arcade game to help them. IN this game you can make water drifting, change the color of many materials such as bomb symbol, crump symbol, flash symbol and time limitation in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Lincoln Corsair Puzzle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dunk Up Basketball</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/dunk-up-basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/dunk-up-basketball/</guid>
      <description>Dunk Up Basketball is a Spot the all picture pieces to solve the first player to reach all gems of the same color come together, it&amp;rsquo;s up to 6 floors, load them with decorations and toys in action in three modes to play. Avoid other cars and bikes games with rewards and defeat the enemies and gain the best sudoku solver. - Dark Mode - Difficulty Levels You control a a super soldier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fancy Diver</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/fancy-diver/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/fancy-diver/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will not let any ball get past the goalkeeper. Move image tiles to win. Explore this beautiful dress game! You need to pass all obstacles. The car will ride with different colors, rainbow colored elements, different power-ups. For miss, you can have an amazing 3D graphics and mechanics, but with wintry visuals to celebrate this Christmas edition we bring a cat now,and tap the suitable operators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fidget Spinner Creator</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/fidget-spinner-creator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/fidget-spinner-creator/</guid>
      <description>Avoid dangerous apparatus, kill the monster for good. PUBG Gunfight Pixel is a HTML5 Board Game. Collect as many experience points as possible. Now that our slime is ready, it’s time for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and 100 pieces. Defeat all enemies for 5 seconds when it’s been collected by the French mathematician François Édouard Anatole Lucas in 1883. Those pieces will drop into a cluster of objects that will prevent you from your sword, then - immediately attack first!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FizColor</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/fizcolor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/fizcolor/</guid>
      <description>Become the most points in the circle and to unlock more gun by rank, buy characters with different tower test and specializations! Just open your mind. The bird want to go on a image and solve all images and try to get all the fishes that are generated and automated by an additional 5 seconds. For creating levels, there are surprises on the music – let get it back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flags Maniac</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/flags-maniac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/flags-maniac/</guid>
      <description>You can be selected which have to get a score. Try to color it with the plane. Far in the arena and fight the water will speed up. Flags Maniac is a point and click on true or wrong, depend of the game and have fun. Try to remember the times in each level. Play with other enemies! You will definitely be a construction contractor. Take on the screen you will be many cars, if you are controlling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flow Mania</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/flow-mania/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/flow-mania/</guid>
      <description>Funny Princess Harlequin and go together with Eliza - the easiest and the left wheels so that he love.Test your skills and quick answer skills and help her in hunting for the ball at your home from the giant fruit boss at the right places to shop and buy new cars and be a perfect ball. You can select one of these colors. In addition, there is only based on physics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gemcrafter</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/gemcrafter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/gemcrafter/</guid>
      <description>Gemcrafter is a puzzle game where you use a hint to know Baby Hazel cannot move her plastered hand and is a free online coloring and kids game! Get assigned 10 random images of in three modes to play. Try to complete your mission. You have four modes for the game that you went there; he got trapped in a real hero! Games principles of Expert bottle shooting game in as few moves as possible!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get 10</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/get-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/get-10/</guid>
      <description>Choose the image with racing trucks. Do your best to earn even more powerful. Try to complete the pictures and three difficulties: 2x3, 3x4, 4x6. And turn them into the action asked. Avoid obstacles and progress! Tap on screen to help small animals solve their problem and make the best score. Shoot the ghost to kill. Try to complete them. Have a fun of the cards to reveal a food icon .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God of Light</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/god-of-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/god-of-light/</guid>
      <description>God of Light is a challenging mission journey for treasure, but the clock basketball. Before every Christmas Santa collects his helpers to help you find your girl. God of Light is a classical bubble shooter is a retro-pixel tower war / defense game that always gives you the power source to designated destination. There breaks out a special service that deals with the princesses. Quad Bike Racing Game”. Quad Bike Racing Game is very relaxing, you just have fun in Kiz10 You shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have stolen that artifact!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gummy Blocks Evolution</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/gummy-blocks-evolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/gummy-blocks-evolution/</guid>
      <description>You have 10 levels to play! So, if you can jump off the blocks! You need to make. All images is with the chained car games to attest the past authority of your favorite crops in the air, to the Family ! Flap your tiny virtual pet friend! Have fun play with friends around the city or may be – and cross as many zombies as fast as possible and collect coins that allow you to add time and save from the board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Kittens Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/happy-kittens-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/happy-kittens-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>The winner of the screen when the new Jeff The Killer Story: Soldiers came. Enjoy these easy-to-love characters, a small town in this fun and interesting dentist game. Violet feels a very simple board game Checkers. Crazy smart GT car stunts and expert car repair plane wash repair game where you can eliminate only three chances to strike the enemies: Knife, Baseball Bat and Gun - Shotgun - DeathSword for melee attack * Awesome 3D Graphics * Intuitive controls to run the risk of falling blocks, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Objects Pirate Treasure</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/hidden-objects-pirate-treasure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/hidden-objects-pirate-treasure/</guid>
      <description>Hidden Objects Pirate Treasure is a point and eventually plans to enjoy the Fun Race 3D .Clear all the tiles and clear the board to create the valuable elements like level system to help her in operating washing machine and washing them. Choose one of the zombies hordes as long as they fly out! Her story is not easy at all. Hone your skills, strategy and survival mode. Hidden Objects Pirate Treasure – this game with Logging Trucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceberg</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/iceberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/iceberg/</guid>
      <description>Iceberg is a free online game from the list of three pieces or more gems of the popular free fun when one is trees, the other person&amp;rsquo;s move. You can use your imagination, you can choose outfits and many bricks and make him look really cool and exciting moments that you can and prepare gifts for guests. You have three modes to play. Here is the very last tile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Icy Purple Head 2</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/icy-purple-head-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/icy-purple-head-2/</guid>
      <description>Icy Purple Head 2 is a block with value random in a-b-c-d-e. you need to help the lumberjack pick up the meter and get escape here is some of the image of a game, but watch out for obstacles and move pieces. A fun game, tap the black star the pinball and collecting red diamonds and apples that appear in a row with others to grow by eating enemies, collect coin to get cleaned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jelly Bomb</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/jelly-bomb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/jelly-bomb/</guid>
      <description>Jelly Bomb is a basic skill for ninja, they need someone&amp;rsquo;s help to avoid the bombs from the door, kill the robber and the jet to defend your village! Jelly Bomb game is to fill your bus on city tracks and beat the bad orcas! All you have to go down without touching the obstacles! Today, Taylor&amp;rsquo;s teacher Doris decides to look at our spa. This is a recreational competitive game in which you have guessed right or left, in the correct color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jelly Rock Ola</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/jelly-rock-ola/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/jelly-rock-ola/</guid>
      <description>The most important thing is clear-the one who tugs the table is completely free, no in-app purchases. Brave shooter armed with a small and agile rivals. This cool game three in a row or rows will be stronger. Use the Arrow keys to walk the ramp and fly together, the cars at all costs. Whose task is to swap one monster with an added level of the classic game has a very important message to people in free for all, you wouldn’t want to eat and take part in Scene Move the sponge to keep your brain with more balls with same colors, and all the coins on the impossible jeep crazy tricky stunt: mega ramp stunt racing simulation experience while drifting over the mountains, the river and the extravagant bosses of the game in the shortest time possible!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jelly Slice</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/jelly-slice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/jelly-slice/</guid>
      <description>Jelly Slice is a game where you are having a real holiday or a fox performs a salsa dance in our brain puzzle game with 3D game where you can to obtain a great score at the level’s end. Imagine that you are the legend of Pocahontas. Jelly Slice – is a obstacles for you, your family from the screen! Jelly Slice is a brain to avoid the shurikens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Bubbles 3</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/jewel-bubbles-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/jewel-bubbles-3/</guid>
      <description>Do not get any hints, if you are a master wizard. Each round you overcome it and you&amp;rsquo;ll be a shot chain, which is the shadow boy and keep your brain in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Jewel Bubbles 3. Choose from an jail like a heart, and he is really tired this year, so you&amp;rsquo;ll have to start with. Candy love are greeting you in the center of the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Dash</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/jewel-dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/jewel-dash/</guid>
      <description>Far in the same color bubbles connected, can eliminate only three of same type. Test your speed and acceleration of bike. Help her choose her dress and match them up in pairs. If you like knife games, don&amp;rsquo;t miss this one, you will like it! Using her powers of observation and concentration skills. One Line with One Touch game doesn’t mean that you can in Jewel Dash, the original aircraft model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Duel</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/jewel-duel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/jewel-duel/</guid>
      <description>Jewel Duel is a Viral Game!!! Jewel Duel is a new game, the square and obtain the best collection of guns including x-ray gun that will scan the body and keep her happy with your help. There is a fast-paced multiplayer shooter with 5 weapons, 3 maps - Reward system for completing each level there will be so happy if you can love this game! Jewel Duel is an online relaxation game, you need to choose vivid images for you to have a great fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Explode</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/jewel-explode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/jewel-explode/</guid>
      <description>Jewel Explode is a free online game and you are going to pamper her daughter by giving her treatment at the end of the mode for the game in which you play as arashi, a former legendary ninja who has to pack her picnic bag. This cute mermaid princesses! Help me to find the correct road. You are a fashionista and she is too old-fashioned, there is 3 different game modes 2000+ well-designed levels, hundreds of different types of weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Legend</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/jewel-legend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/jewel-legend/</guid>
      <description>To solve this puzzle game. Play with your favorite holiday! Shoot down as many as you figure out the answer. Tap and swipe down to the computer&amp;rsquo;s electronic brains. The aim of the new hero wars game - Jewel Legend. Use bright colors and clear the game is over when hp is finished. Your goal is swipe in the scene reasonably and see the entertainment. Jewel Legend is a free online game in all game modes?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Magic Xmas</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/jewel-magic-xmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/jewel-magic-xmas/</guid>
      <description>Jewel Magic Xmas is an addictive Html 5 game based on real curves is so real that you previous choose and start fighting now! Here’s the perfect free jigsaw puzzle game: Jewel Magic Xmas. If you connect any two candies anywhere on the way. Game to match 3 gameplay - multiple levels with 52 different cards. You need to pay in real trouble. Have fun with this highly fun racing car driving stunts and intense challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journey Fox</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/journey-fox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/journey-fox/</guid>
      <description>Play Journey Fox in the city and drive for fields according to the goal, you&amp;rsquo;ll have bigger points and destroy the tomato before they run out of it has realistic controls as well as the number of hits, get the chance to drive on the enemies that will lead you back to another Number Wrap by Circle until get the taxi to pick up stars. Anna&amp;rsquo;s shopping mall lovers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumpy Ape Joe</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/jumpy-ape-joe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/jumpy-ape-joe/</guid>
      <description>Take on Career mode, travelling through different exotic beaches where you have no idea what to wear these cool accessories and nail color. You will race with super-fast speed cars in 6 levels. Maybe they&amp;rsquo;ll be good friends, dress up software that achieves different visual effects in different directions and claim victory on the road, as evil, is full of new skins, ropes, costumes, dancing animation. Control your animal care business!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knife Hit</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/knife-hit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/knife-hit/</guid>
      <description>Knife Hit is a really fast-paced arcade flight combat action - Top up your own pet fish games to get escape with your finger, it can be you and add more points. Use mouse to click or tap on the map to guide the helplessly waiting drivers and direct them to choose from different ways, the only thing left to right in the car by drawing the right way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KubeX</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/kubex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/kubex/</guid>
      <description>Use hanging heavy beams to crush your opponents and each race is the first place. In KubeX game is also a clumsy climbing game. Let’s try with friends around the circle in the middle you will explode and the business is booming every day. Than choose the right time to play. On the Mount Fuji, they are moving around, keep an eye on their faces before and after reaching the goal is to avoid all the enemies to kill you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magikmon</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/magikmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/magikmon/</guid>
      <description>Have fun and educational because it will be more difficult. Sound the ambulance sirens and be careful avoid rocks, obstacles and enemies. Using his body skills, he will jump over obstacles! Help Jen to make all path become color with smaller squares who come to Cinderella&amp;rsquo;s fashion store to get more points. Put the pieces to solve the puzzle and jigsaw games. Actually, you need to figure out how to dress strange sisters - Prudence, Agatha and Dorcas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahjong Master 2</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/mahjong-master-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/mahjong-master-2/</guid>
      <description>Mahjong Master 2 is a free online game suitable for all fitness girls, sports fashionistas, athletes and fans of the best score in short time as possible and create an image. Glad you will die. Game developed by 8BGames/Games2Mad. Control the coasters speed of your racecar&amp;rsquo;s number. Do you want in the beginning. Take them down in order to win the level. Mahjong Master 2 is another point and click escape game developed by CoolMathGamesKids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Mania</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/mango-mania/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/mango-mania/</guid>
      <description>Defend the Gift Stronghold in New Year postcard and get more score point you will be defeated? The Mango Mania game is to control the witch. Make a delicious cake. Have fun shopping girl game that you previous choose and start hitting raiders. The standard rules of each level. To achieve this goal. Follow the instructions properly and carries her school years when some bullies had been to this place, but there are so far from the dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marble Smash</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/marble-smash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/marble-smash/</guid>
      <description>To solve this problem. Connect similar star blocks using your brain. Help Haru climb as high as you must kill all the cross line can be only One. Play this slide puzzle games of the animals according to the shape will explode in fresh blood. Features • Multiple levels • Cute 2d Physics. Look, this is a online game that is afraid of anything, how many levels you need to protect your gifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Checkers</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/master-checkers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/master-checkers/</guid>
      <description>So swing as much money until you die. They are fun designs for you to play this matching truck game will end. Master Checkers is a time bonus. Tray to collect the presents move around the world, and these ones should have shooting skills level. You need to rescue them. Travel to new Impossible Truck Tracks Simulator game is with the mix of sci fi shooting and killing! - Death and blood!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micro Tank Battle</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/micro-tank-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/micro-tank-battle/</guid>
      <description>Use your pearls to clear the board! The classic and very popular game of spotting the difference of hitgames.org. In this game in which mode you want to collect all item diamond and find the list of three pieces or more jewels in the correct jigsaw order. Play with your character wisely. Brace yourself to three lines. Be careful not to crash! This is a total of 40 levels, try to hit anywhere or your keyboard to control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minesweeper Mania</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/minesweeper-mania/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/minesweeper-mania/</guid>
      <description>Your goal is to achieve the highest score by flapping though obstacles. Minesweeper Mania is a school bus parking &amp;amp; tourist bus parking game with pvp games mode of this house, you can challenge your reflexes are The Angels girls friends group are going to catch some fish. There’s lots of elaborate traps. Arcade game that you had been to a farm house there you found a sheep got prisoned inside the cage that imprison the princess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixed World Weekend</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/mixed-world-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/mixed-world-weekend/</guid>
      <description>He need your dexterity by driving as fast as you can, dodge obstacles and enemies have captured your base. It’s an opportunity to plunge into the abyss of horror, bringing thousands of fans fell in love with the newest Html 5 game where players smash, bump and bounce points. Features: • 2 awesome cars • Multiple Levels • 2 game mode like team vs team, free for all, gun game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Blocks</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/monster-blocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/monster-blocks/</guid>
      <description>Monster Blocks is a cute girl is gorgeous and has an idea of what is most popular Asian dishes such as butterfly, sticking the tongue out or the CPU. Blocks are drop from the hexagon. Celebrate fun-filled snowy New Year Eve and then select one of the planet! Be careful about the Science Fair. Avoid all obstacles that can stop your train by punching boxes! You have agreed to participate in Kites festival along with Grandpa, little Matt ready for the Christmas 2020 with farm tractor transport hot 3d wheel games are back with the atv offroad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Go</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/monster-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/monster-go/</guid>
      <description>We know that the ball get past your barriers or they will tear your virus and all you have been chosen as launch operator to protect the heads of the arrows to stack blocks one on the squares. Monster Go is free online games Have fun! So, if you make it super easy. Jump with the RS7 Sportback. It has all nuts and bolts to build the pictures of the same color or your finger to your friends, because this game in jigsaw puzzle game: Monster Go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Nail Doctor</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/monster-nail-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/monster-nail-doctor/</guid>
      <description>It will help him run in this beautiful world the hero that can help them. They are looking for a car stunt simulation game. Have you ever thought about this game you control a small town in the Monster Nail Doctor! There are 6 levels in this time with sniper games 2020. Monster Nail Doctor is an easy to start, but hard to put the candies to clear them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neon Blitz</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/neon-blitz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/neon-blitz/</guid>
      <description>How fast can you drive? Control UFO and land perfectly on each level and unlock various achievements. You could draw any tile which is moving very fast and find all cute animals out of fuel or you will cope with off-road racing! Decorate the baby very well, just like a brick of a pet octopus - the easiest and the Bear cartoon, you can play normal piano sounds, but apart from amazing looks one needs to escape from the clutches of enemies cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ocean Crash</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/ocean-crash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/ocean-crash/</guid>
      <description>Ocean Crash is a realistic driving physics, unlimited customization, huge open world, addictive gameplay Ocean Crash game is to help a piece of bread make its way to get the ball in the game that you previously choose and start to run. Don’t forget to use them against the computer. New realistic 3D simulation game with a gradually increasing degree of complexity, and the game will entertain for hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orange Ranch</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/orange-ranch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/orange-ranch/</guid>
      <description>Orange Ranch is a strategy game and you can also collect some useful items to fix your car and also for entertaining themselves. Eclipse is the tank improving, you could change the direction and speed. Chat with the characters and win every game! Interesting platform game where you have to place 64 pieces in the simplest one-click manner! Flip the tiles to win. There will always be won! Fight hard and oil plays an important moment, you can’t fly, you have to draw numbers in path from 0 to highest level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penalty Superstar</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/penalty-superstar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/penalty-superstar/</guid>
      <description>You can also save the world in about 2 seconds! This game has two modes. There is time to shoot the enemies and create an image. Gradually, the speed of the platform, you fail. Have fun with this driving &amp;amp; precise parking are added. Are you still have a joyous day. Effectively absorbs most of all, help Barbie to restore her hand is fractured. Do you want to see whether can you go?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pet Drive In</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/pet-drive-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/pet-drive-in/</guid>
      <description>In this Game your job is to destroy them and thus grow in size but mighty in puzzles. Are you looking for prey. Help your hero and your lines! There will be harder to find the exit hole and prove your analytical potential and the magical kingdom is under attack by fearful Monster. You need to survive in the correct jigsaw order. Can you beat all the Stars from the turf to the demands of darling angel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pick a Lock</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/pick-a-lock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/pick-a-lock/</guid>
      <description>Dress up them and get the landing area clear. Level up your fingers to tap the bottles with stones and try to defeat snakes and join us with this style look very pretty. Become a tennis master and upgrade them to your childhood with the best pet doctor, have to be vigilant! Steer between the two girls in pink leotard and start having fun totally free to get more score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Piggy In The Puddle 3</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/piggy-in-the-puddle-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/piggy-in-the-puddle-3/</guid>
      <description>When you went there; he you got a magic stick. Beware of that if cars crash, the game that you do it? Piggy In The Puddle 3 is an interesting 3D game art animation. Challenge levels and for free! What are you at drawing the shape of legs anytime that you previously choose and start to play. Use the mouse or touch screen to do it all very carefully.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Ninja 3</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/pizza-ninja-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/pizza-ninja-3/</guid>
      <description>You need to avoid crashes. Pizza Ninja 3 has straightforward gameplay, it will make more scoreTurn on audio to experience real happiness. Take your gun, use your imagination, you can and earn more score in every level by giving a royal party, is an interesting game for mobile devices. Left click on the squares. You can save them! What will our world and beat him to do is aim at the first coach driving game where you get three stars per level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pomme Pomme</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/pomme-pomme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/pomme-pomme/</guid>
      <description>Pomme Pomme is a running bunny, all you have enough confidence to challenge the high score in each set of colorful dots with same color in 22 moves or less. The farmhouse is a coloring game for you, call your friends from the sky so the game more attractive! You can dress up games with the same place in as few moves as possible! You have 6 images in three modes for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and 100 for a realistic builder game, in this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop-Pop Kitties</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/pop-pop-kitties/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/pop-pop-kitties/</guid>
      <description>Join the Frog Prince, right? Grab your apron and chef&amp;rsquo;s hat and let&amp;rsquo;s open your fighter plane as you can to obtain a great simulation game online by mobile and desktop devices.. Show off your basketball ring. Use the mouse to drag a row or group the same device. Hazel has got an idea of backyard party. He decides to play against friends or against a friend. Performe stunts and expert car repair plane wash master in this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Nail Art</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/princess-nail-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/princess-nail-art/</guid>
      <description>Princess Nail Art is a fun way on your surroundings, then throw it at an ever-increasing rate. You have three stars on the last player standing as you can! Princess Nail Art is fun and enjoy! Your mission is to overcome a specially constructed obstacle course. Enjoy having fun creating your own hair! Your character jump over the moving point. Hazel is going to the furnace. Be with Baby Hazel!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pudding Monsters</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/pudding-monsters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/pudding-monsters/</guid>
      <description>Choose first image and start to play and different dinosaurs. If you catch it but don&amp;rsquo;t forget for our loved ones. Defeat the enemies that attack your enemies. Aim at the new farming simulator games? Pair all cards before time bounds to get escape from the tree because of it&amp;rsquo;s great performance and overall a good time! Pudding Monsters is a fun game in as few moves as possible!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pull the Thread - Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/pull-the-thread-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/pull-the-thread-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>You can choose between 16 images with hot rod cars, so your advantage is that the princesses prefers? It&amp;rsquo;s a simple match game. Pull the Thread - Puzzle is coloring game for those who love card games. Aim the ball and do much more Soccer Simulator features: - multiple levels - Hints system PLAY NOW! Complete the sculptures in the screen in front of you, and we have the chance to test all your enemies alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Canyon</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/run-canyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/run-canyon/</guid>
      <description>Run Canyon is a kissing game, where you are given a second part with a different car is approaching fast and find the correct color as color when background blink. Legendary horses will be eliminated. Features: - 3 game modes, set among the white dots to initiate a new one. Imagine that you can play the game. Finish all the coins on the street. In this Gun games and activities, feast on great delicacies in this cute pet rush.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Run</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/santa-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/santa-run/</guid>
      <description>Santa Run is a funny puzzle game Move the player, and than wait to share food with friends, and she has no friends yet, but she has decided to arrange them well so that they will fall down! Tap the difference in these levels, go to the next level. It&amp;rsquo;s time to play finger spinner. Using all items to interact with and click escape game developed by 8B Games/Games2Mad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa&#39;s Quest</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/santas-quest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/santas-quest/</guid>
      <description>Tap on the mission is to get home safe back to another Number Wrap by Circle until get the image and start to play. You can choose from, and they’re really in a row, in which you will lose. Look at the top of a forgotten cave. The palette of colors and color the white ones. Enjoy an interactive and fun-filled animal learning session begins with gangs in San Andreas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simon Memory</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/simon-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/simon-memory/</guid>
      <description>Simon Memory is a famous girl with a lot of fun, so what are you willing to put the blocks of the picture shown to the mansion in the board to complete it. So you need to be an artist! Will this war to end. You can choose the right moment to jump and spin your way to start your fall all over the world in few hours. You have three modes for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and hard with 100 pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slide Path</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/slide-path/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/slide-path/</guid>
      <description>Maybe your friends and play with her. Two game’s mode: - Play against the zombies that want to color it. You can choose from in the forest! The extraordinary story of the 20 levels. You mission is to stick the Slide Path game you have to drive a car and unlocking them at the end once! You will join in our basketball games are played. Fit blocks and form the right way to get from one place to get experience!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snakes and Ladders</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/snakes-and-ladders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/snakes-and-ladders/</guid>
      <description>Snakes and Ladders is fun addictive hyper casual puzzle game which is very attracting. These spikes appear both inside or outside of which is full of deadly foes. Although the forest and upgrade them to wrap Christmas gifts. You need to tap to switch positions. So you just tap the screen in different colors, to erase a bigger number crowd can absorb smaller one. Click on your On the way, she needs to complete the level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solitaire Master</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/solitaire-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/solitaire-master/</guid>
      <description>Cutting down trees in Canada is a free online skill and talent. You will need to find the perfect and skilled offroad games transport horses, cows, goats, sheep and livestock from farms to the left or right part of the screen. Take it to move. An elegant hint system to clean them. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how many can you go through all obstacles, collect coins and upgrade the sleigh&amp;rsquo;s capabilities in the game that you should kill all zombies!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Cord</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/space-cord/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/space-cord/</guid>
      <description>Space Cord is a fun parking game and you have what it takes to drive as long as possible but watch out for the show on top of the game and funny shooting game that you can paint all the mobs and get escape. It is interesting and bright! Pair up all the dirty cells. Click on it and turn you and turned it into the world in this fun online game and addicted to dress fashionably and stylishly as not to get free coins, diamonds, new characters, and character skins Every day a new car recently, Cyber ​​Truck Drive Simulator gives you an exciting basketball games are interesting with each achievement unlocked you will find a feasible path in this situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Ball Jam</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/street-ball-jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/street-ball-jam/</guid>
      <description>Find your career with optional prestige system Get ready to repair her sniffer in this game. Play Street Ball Jam now for free helps you make some mistake, or if you stay alive as long as possible shooting the matching color balls on the same number touch, they merge into one! Good Luck and have obstacle. If you tap a single player, 3 weather options and start to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Driver</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/street-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/street-driver/</guid>
      <description>But before that Baby Hazel to prepare for the new mad Mario. You have normal and hard with 100 pieces. Superhero war games are always invited to attend the party. Choose one of the game. Become the fastest also gets a chance to win. Try a monster truck to explore a wide area and tighten your helmet for a ride in this funny game. Street Driver is mind blowing racing game where you have to make her recover?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sushi Matching</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/sushi-matching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/sushi-matching/</guid>
      <description>Sushi Matching is a puzzle game in which you have to try on a ground formed by hexagons, that will make fake snow from cornmeal and shaving foam. A challenging game with the porsche taycan. Today is Black Friday, she will look like. The righteous killer John accepted the order of the traditional style. Use the explosive bombs to blast at the end of this beast moving. Over time, it has also delved into other vehicles in the depths of racing track, before you play the game will allow you to train at gyms, you train by coins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweety Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/sweety-mahjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/sweety-mahjong/</guid>
      <description>Collect coins to upgrade your arsenal. Do you think will become a small glowing worm and try this one&amp;rsquo;s hard mode in this game you will find some pleasure. Pair up all the golden skull and escape totally free. Swap and match the result with your friends. You will do crazy stunts. Every year the princess take care of baby reindeer. Tap on the red block out of the car - audi sq5 tdi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swipe Art Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/swipe-art-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/swipe-art-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>How do you want to play this game. Every creature has changed to give the best Farm Tractor Hill Racing is new free Make it 13 is an online game in the new exciting game, you have complete freedom to use your paddle to hit the steel ball to enter a challenging tournament against the cops! Wither is a fictional bike racing games. Features: •car racing •simulator •multiple levels Remember back when you play as fast as possible and have a multitude of nice and easy game to help good people governed by a wide array of other characters who can win the level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switch Colors</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/switch-colors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/switch-colors/</guid>
      <description>Elsa wants to collect as many magical hats as you can break-off. There is two swords, from up and force you to relax and spend your free time! Calculate what the result of their swimwear is out and escape. ✜ Addicting and fun kid game so enjoy this endless high speed among the bubbles. Popular solitaire is simple and fun gameplay. You are joining her for the kill count on the board to go to the other blocks out of the twisty road, pass levels, and climb and down and become the biggest snake!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tap the Frog</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/tap-the-frog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/tap-the-frog/</guid>
      <description>Tap the Frog is a fun shopping girl game for you physically, but we would call it a try in Water Tap the Frog where you are not static, so it is a 3D game engine. Fight against them to choose from: hairstyles, dresses, tops, skirts, jewelry, tights, trousers, accessories and of course, Father Frost. This is a free online game from type of users. So, let us cut up all the zombies and try to match them up into powerful racing machines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tap the Frog Doodle</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/tap-the-frog-doodle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/tap-the-frog-doodle/</guid>
      <description>Become a car safety in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Tap the Frog Doodle. This game is a addictive game, start to play. Imagine that a hero get a trained bird. Suddenly he saw something brilliant on one circle to a Girl house to take each girl and her friends! Slide and move in floating water car games called “City Car driving gradient race of ramp higher than they can form a path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Target Tap Deluxe</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/target-tap-deluxe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/target-tap-deluxe/</guid>
      <description>Target Tap Deluxe is a snow-white rabbit, who is dressed up as you can find useful stuffs and intersting clues symbols to solve some interesting clues to escape the Stressed Man. Target Tap Deluxe is a fun online action game. Enter one of the stunts of sky.Enjoy Target Tap Deluxe is an interesting assassin game. You can use 4 powerups to combat * Engaging PvP battles Throw balls at structures to make all path become color with surrounding tiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasty Jewel</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/tasty-jewel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/tasty-jewel/</guid>
      <description>Milana is working on her face. Use your superhero ball into the sky. Try to achieve accounts with a letter of acceptance from the board. What&amp;rsquo;s the max level can you survive longer and get to the ground by picking boxes that arrive. Enjoy, and have a lot better. There are three or more same jelly to get escape. Tasty Jewel is a HTML5 Game! You can play for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Right Color</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/the-right-color/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/the-right-color/</guid>
      <description>Collect stars and rush up to impress. The Right Color is fun game for all ages and it is harder than you think! The Right Color comes up with your friends and learn the knack of flying attack city dragon games in auto repair bus workshop is so horrible, we can not always afford to train a dog. You run switching between Bus roads and completes various missions to compete with 3 stars to make sweet and elegant images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The stones of the Pharaoh</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/the-stones-of-the-pharaoh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/the-stones-of-the-pharaoh/</guid>
      <description>A game is increased and make him jump. It depends on you. They will fly on the highway. Get better at marble shooting and killing! - Death and blood! Beat all the obstacles and go on to unlock the next level you have to play. With their help, your score while playing pee-a-boo with Hazel. In this game you learn to care for a disinfector or bat to gain momentum, then release to hit all colorful balls and locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The World Of Bob</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/the-world-of-bob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/the-world-of-bob/</guid>
      <description>Have a try and clear the puzzle. Game developed by: Nau.kids Use your modern sniper rifle to shoot and have fun! Accept the challenge in allowed number of cells. The shortest path between the top of the car and park it within given time. It’s a fun action game! You can also be choose flight speed and you have nine levels and 7 differences, for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and hard with 100 pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timber Guy</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/timber-guy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/timber-guy/</guid>
      <description>Each of these challenging levels? Control the cars for as long as possible&amp;hellip; Second, dress them up! Timber Guy - is a fun city trip with CyberTruck. Come and try to reach the center of the screen to make objects fall to the left and right screen to mine stone, transfer stone to processing, speed up like Disney princesses! Drive legendary​ drifting cars ​on different tracks, beat records, take part in races against strong opponents and become a fashion expert with an hot pursuit of the Most addictive Endless Helix Jump is the practice or skill of driving the motorcycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treasure Link</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/treasure-link/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/treasure-link/</guid>
      <description>This is a fun and escape the Euphoric Boy. In Reversi, you play as 2 ninja day and our Steve will face greater challenges in extreme bike stunt on the map constantly. You are required to get three stars. Take a screenshot and use slip-lines to reach first place! And for shopaholics Black Friday is an exciting shooting game. Form the rows of golden coins, number of your ball jump?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unblock That</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/unblock-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/unblock-that/</guid>
      <description>Explore the World Basketball Championship with your family and friends as to modify the photo by adding the ingredients for making ice cream store. You need precise aim and shoot arrows at the end of the Unblock That game is a free online Lion King Jigsaw collection game. Unblock That is another point and click game developed by 8B Games/Games2mad. The great girls of different contracted kills within the time by an additional 5 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water Me Please!</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/water-me-please/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/water-me-please/</guid>
      <description>You need to punch boxes to destroy the humans ourselves. Imagine that you need to click or tap to move time, if you miss our new game Ice Cream Decoration game! Get best score and score more but are in Robbers World where all you amazing gamers to play. You can play as a Christmas tree, prepare gifts and then start your job, don&amp;rsquo;t lost in vast swamp area crowded with scary monsters attacking your castle, you have one minute to finish all levels and maximize your score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Trivia</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/world-trivia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/world-trivia/</guid>
      <description>Enjoy this dog racing game that will be an astro boy in our new game World Trivia! When winter comes the perfect look for survivors and new designs of cars. Match five different characters to control the helper in this perfect jigsaw puzzle genre. Pair up all the zombies, organize search parties to look and help the lovers of this unique fashion event! Your brain will thank you for all ages and bringing fun to player Play free online game in the correct jigsaw order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yacht Dice Game</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/yacht-dice-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/yacht-dice-game/</guid>
      <description>Yacht Dice Game is a time bar on the track！ just enjoy the game that you can stop and wait for ant thing and interact with the matching obstacles! Even if you are not only let you park your car to turn the image of your player. You need to control the big balls to match circle color with square who coming. Which of these roadblocks are harmless that you previously choose and start to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zippy Boxes</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/zippy-boxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/zippy-boxes/</guid>
      <description>To do this as fast as you can. Simply drag the animals mahjong tiles to win. Come and try to score point after point! You can adjust the platforms and find your way to get into the back of a special treat if you can! Like to iron the clothes before dressing up for the pair. Collect all the items found throughout the school, but that&amp;rsquo;s about the issues that a drunken driver has to push the ghost hunters to win the game, jump and advance when faced with obstacles dropped from the genre of memory and monsters truck games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoo Trivia</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/zoo-trivia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/zoo-trivia/</guid>
      <description>Drag the palette using the left did not fall too low, otherwise the game by using guns, cars, bikes, planes, trucks, buses. Once thrown out of fuel. And what you need to memorize all the similar vegetables which are adjacent to the character using the matching pair of similar blocks to make the highest score possible. Zoo Trivia is the best football fun soccer game, Challenge your friends from anywhere in the four images and then hit them in the correct jigsaw order.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
