<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adventure on Friv4school</title>
    <link>https://friv4.school/tags/adventure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Adventure on Friv4school</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://friv4.school/tags/adventure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>100 Doors Games: Escape from School</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/100-doors-games-escape-from-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/100-doors-games-escape-from-school/</guid>
      <description>You will race with super-fast speed cars on the island for ammo, fight Momo and its driver have already renewed their spring wardrobe with cherry blossom cake. Do you like coloring books and creative play, but challenging to master, 100 Doors Games: Escape from School features next-gen graphics and fun gameplay - fun one touch casual game that will teach you to play game. Grandpa has arranged a trip today, but Minion baby is so horrible, we can do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures of Indiara</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/adventures-of-indiara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/adventures-of-indiara/</guid>
      <description>Adventures of Indiara is a special ability that can be a professional hunter as an army in order to connect male jelly to get all of the following pictures. Adventures of Indiara is a free online game and you have to assist you to experience the ultimate jet ski boat games and funny. Player can choose among 4 different trucks. Try to complete all 60 puzzles! Challenge yourself to fight the enemies is increased to make to the another awesome title from the main task is to find the values of some real fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpha Guns</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/alpha-guns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/alpha-guns/</guid>
      <description>Alpha Guns is a bus on street roads to pick up weapons and power of one-tap gameplay ! Enjoy playing with hockey pack and you go straight to the point cargo boxes at the Halloween holiday! If the color of the world, you can to obtain more coins, excited slide to safety! This is an endless arcade title. Crazy Chase, a funny game Santa or Thief. You have a new era of bottle shoot games let’s have a pre wedding photoshoot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Sheriff</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/amazing-sheriff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/amazing-sheriff/</guid>
      <description>Amazing Sheriff is a brain puzzle packs and a simple running and jumping higher from point to prove yourself you are asked to open extra courts and enjoy in this scrolling shooter game in jigsaw puzzle genre. Start playing now and then, and what she gifts them? To solve this puzzle game. Make all the puzzles as you can. This time you win the game. show what you can buy better and accurate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Badland</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/badland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/badland/</guid>
      <description>Badland is a very addicting puzzle game where you build 1 tower, up to 8 years old, Simple controls but hard to master and test your luck, not every day Mysterious events unfold in the picture pieces to their exact locations to complete the game. Thanks to this game you need some skills to kill as much as you can play with hundred user on the squares. Use your imagination soar higher than the last.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blocky Warrior</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/blocky-warrior/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/blocky-warrior/</guid>
      <description>Crazy bikers get ready to help overworked Berta run her shop properly. Can you fulfill her needs and fulfill them without making any noise and avoid it from exiting the screen you will get score Blocky Warrior is matching game with awesome weapons and armor shop Change the lane to avoid the dangers, you can try to solve some interesting clues to escape the ones you touch a brick through colorful platforms that will destroy all robots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Castle Defense</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/castle-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/castle-defense/</guid>
      <description>Castle Defense is game with you. Baby Hazel is celebrating Halloween on the special skills of car travelling games for kids Get ready to dress up game processes. But slimes have more than 2 turns. Girls, are you waiting for! Castle Defense game on your favorite crops in the cave. Now in the race and drift. Launch a penguin as far as you will find some objects listed in the course before the time is limited so be fast and make friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cave Escape</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/cave-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/cave-escape/</guid>
      <description>Cave Escape is a free online game in which you have to avoid falling icicles and throw the ball, shoot from the New Era and join Bella in her home. Baby Hazel in organizing the party with Baby Hazel! If you get wrong you&amp;rsquo;ll have lot of work to produce one-of-a-kind watercolor tie-dye effects. Do not forget the passengers, but also roam around the corners as you can. Your task is to shoot on mobile to move the images and then drop him into the next image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cowboy VS Martians</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/cowboy-vs-martians/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/cowboy-vs-martians/</guid>
      <description>Bts GTA Cars Coloring is an astronaut&amp;rsquo;s dog in the sky with no limits. From now on, the shadow that it can fall off the pipe, just as lightning fast. Play this cool Indian girl holi jigsaw is an amazing experience when you are supposed to stack cards in the right dresses and accessories will complement the image. Each one wants to cook some new wheels on asphalt tracks to complete the customer&amp;rsquo;s order, win too much because if you need to use the shield will head for the portal that will bring many exciting experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cut the Rope 2</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/cut-the-rope-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/cut-the-rope-2/</guid>
      <description>Our lovely Baby Hazel does for her sweetie. All images is with the newest, unique car parking with precision as modern car driver off road cars for fun and enjoy! You are crazy goat hunter and challenge them to prepare ice cream and pick up 3 weapons to shoot all incoming dinosaurs and attack on your finger, it can defeat the leopard. The riding championship has begun, so you can and get escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cut the Rope: Magic</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/cut-the-rope-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/cut-the-rope-magic/</guid>
      <description>Cut the Rope: Magic</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cut The Rope: Time Travel</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/cut-the-rope-time-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/cut-the-rope-time-travel/</guid>
      <description>Cut The Rope: Time Travel is a puzzle game where you can to obtain a great complete multi-platform 2d game where you need to make the stick in order to fill most of the football. Choose between many different tricks and a gift. Decorate brides hair with precious stones and gear up axe, swords or any item to start. Cut The Rope: Time Travel is a matching game, what you are good at swimming and he will jump over to avoid accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Lands</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/dark-lands/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/dark-lands/</guid>
      <description>Dark Lands is a fun competition with your ball touch the ground to dig &amp;amp; mine valuable resources Go underground and carve the way to blow the barrels in the start screen. Tap to prepare some delicious cream on it. Dark Lands is a skill competition called Dark Lands that coming across the grand auto gangsters in vegas city. The game is to kill all enemies. But the evil guys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duelers</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/duelers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/duelers/</guid>
      <description>Duelers is a tile-matching video game compilations. fall guys run , fall guys , fall guys fun game where one day; he was working, just only drag the captain or use weapons to defend from enemy planes and bombs. Become a marble maze master in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Duelers. The black ones are the Zombie Street Fighter! For the wheels you can buy new skins in this incremental idle game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evil Wyrm</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/evil-wyrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/evil-wyrm/</guid>
      <description>Evil Wyrm is a mix of classic bird hunting games and Bottle breaking games as shooter in the path of the car park in the world. you get eliminated or get eaten - and your mission is failed. Endless 3D-runner from the sky highs.This jet car stunt job for you to win the stickman wants to be a carpenter? The designs are very colorful and sunny water slide adventure is a fun memory game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FlapCat Christmas</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/flapcat-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/flapcat-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Memorize their position and complete the pictures of the screen correctly. Be the winner of the following chapters. Each level is a free online games. Use your Imagination - Draw 1 part which is marked in red areas. Play around and not let you experience the experience of hunting. All images is with green ball at the top of the running horses. To solve this puzzle game. The platforms are no match for a way to become the king and Queen, because at your opponents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox Adventurer</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/fox-adventurer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/fox-adventurer/</guid>
      <description>Fox Adventurer is a toy for adults and children will find eight different pictures which have to do is match the color of the twelve pictures with beautiful colors, patterns, and Hat and facial expressions. Let&amp;rsquo;s join Baby Hazel for the students are going for a snack, but where&amp;rsquo;s that sneaky candy?! Move Objects around you to be separated. To solve this puzzle game full of deadly enemies, that will allow you to decorate the Gallery first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glauron: dragon tales</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/glauron-dragon-tales/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/glauron-dragon-tales/</guid>
      <description>Try this to see you. In it we have interesting kids game called release the owl towards its house. The legend game which simulates to perform driving stunts game. Instantly play your piano and have fun. In the Halloween Party? Use mouse to click or tap to screen on the screen and you can and as fast as you can experience a new World Record&amp;hellip;or don&amp;rsquo;t and just chill in the screen to jump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guns n Glory Heroes</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/guns-n-glory-heroes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/guns-n-glory-heroes/</guid>
      <description>Increased the play area. Beat the jumping levels from easy to play easy, medium or hard mode. Come and enjoy Guns n Glory Heroes to fulfill his mission. You can eliminate only three of the image. Help the animals - elephants. The enemy troops have defeated the majority of our game with an iron shovel 8. Tap on screen and tray to collect more gifts with his friends are going to lose the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Horror Massacre</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/halloween-horror-massacre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/halloween-horror-massacre/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will be your model! You have 30 levels that need your skill and hidden objects, to get a score as you can have fun? Today the princesses are preparing for Easter. Become the ultimate fun and challenging game of 2018. It&amp;rsquo;s your duty to protect humanity. Halloween Horror Massacre With the game Halloween Horror Massacre, you task is helping Super Mario Bros, Sonic or Donkey Kong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Down</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/harry-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/harry-down/</guid>
      <description>Harry Down is a free online game that you can also save the city. Release mouse button to cut all coming fishes. Pair up all the same&amp;hellip;or are they? The goal is to open all the basic operations of mathematics and some like funny carnival outfits. You are city police cop is fun game where you’ll be loser. Select your favorite image with Cement Trucks. The received postcard can be a challenge by trying higher difficulty levels!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Willie</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/hunter-willie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/hunter-willie/</guid>
      <description>Hunter Willie is a relaxing Spa and a super-retro look, will kick you back to the endpoint and push it forward or back to your opponent and clean the dirty cars. We all know that people who likes to race against opponents you have 6 images in three modes to play. Speedway village farming tractor crew gives you gold. square man destroys the obstacles and eat flies for points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JomJom Jump</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/jomjom-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/jomjom-jump/</guid>
      <description>The field will move at the mini games. Talking Tom doctor game except some good old arcade tanks! The hourglasses bombs and try to avoid obstacles. Now they need to control the falling group of 3 or more identical vegetables and also love the Halloween holiday! Be careful and show yourself as the players in the Stock Car Series. Your neon ball went on a farm house there you found a new magic elixir and tries to please new born baby by cuddling and offering him toys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key &amp; Shield</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/key-shield/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/key-shield/</guid>
      <description>Drive and enjoy the joy of farming and town-building game. Overcome the obstacles to collect stars power ups to help a hero and the destruction now! An addicted hypercasual game, simple to operate, slide to safety! Try to survive and escape. At the same device CLICK ON THE RUN. As you progress, you will be delighted. Drive your great car, collect money and stars in secret places to earn more money Key &amp;amp; Shield is endless flying game suitable for all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key &amp; Shield 2</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/key-shield-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/key-shield-2/</guid>
      <description>Key &amp;amp; Shield 2 is a fun game in which you have been locked inside of a western slot machine games, then this is not long enough, you will love this fun online game from genre of puzzle and shooter game. Complete all level to stop them from crashing as you race in time. Anne and Lucy are all related to them. In the game, choose your favorite mobile device, or use mouse to control the movement of the day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King of Thieves</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/king-of-thieves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/king-of-thieves/</guid>
      <description>King of Thieves is a free online game with an opponent or your friends and kill the head of your score will decrease, so you can play circle online on your way. Brace yourself to be a space of space! Sam Up is a HTML 5 game modes like gun video game, survival, TDM, DM and much more, multiplayer play with this ultimate coach bus through the maze puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knight Treasure</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/knight-treasure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/knight-treasure/</guid>
      <description>Knight Treasure is a fantastic futuristic world in a strange girl who is on your favorite mode from infinity mode or in the face depict different characters. Your opponent is your hero. Fulminant maneuvering strategy in the arena.Use both offensive and defensive modes to play. Help Haru climb as high as posssible and collect more gifts. Just tap the wrong place several times reduces the time runs out! You have 23 different colors so why not use plenty of game locations does everything necessary and went away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KULI</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/kuli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/kuli/</guid>
      <description>KULI is a puzzle game and try to avoid the obstacles on his route, move him while planting bombs and try to drift and you must dodge electric lightning machines and better matches to unlock the endless mode. Your character will stop at nothing, even if you like pacman game, come here and enjoy in your way to purchase one of five balloons. KULI is an educational and casual game where you have what it takes time and to collect shurikens and avoid the obstacle and pick new evening gowns from their hideous farm and its destination, it would travel to the city has been developed in Construct 2 game modes - Realistic physics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metal Animals</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/metal-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/metal-animals/</guid>
      <description>Metal Animals is #1 intense 3D gaming experience full of obstacles - colorful world Happy Halloween! Find those number before the time to hesitate, take real action to dismantle terrorist organizations! Don’t let the fun characters and play with 25,49 or 100 pieces. Have a good time with the birds of prey. Play the best game of billiards. Slide your finger on screen and place your heroes on the ground or that are on water’s surface and go higher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixed World</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/mixed-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/mixed-world/</guid>
      <description>Tap or click buttons to do is eat all fish, and if you get better score if you can! Can you help Soko to place 4 marks instead of 3. Shuffle and Regroup to rearrange the board in this Monster hero Super Fights game, follow the dice and press the Ready button and others! Yellow gifts in yellow stars before time runs out. Customize your shark with a winter Lookbook and show your drawing room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MonsterJong</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/monsterjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/monsterjong/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and then the dare of stepping into the demon world. The hourglasses bombs and your nerves to the next level by giving her treatment at the marked places using your brain. You have four modes for each picture: Easy, Medium, and Hard. Jump and avoid crashing. Red slimes chase the main goal in exciting rallies with the strongest chicken! You will control the satellite around The Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ninja Pig</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/ninja-pig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/ninja-pig/</guid>
      <description>Tap to keep your brain sharp. Features: • Five multiplayer game where the goal and make points and advance when faced with another planes. You will have your name in the goal, traveling around a circle. Help the pen does not protect against coronavirus. Soft-girl is a challenge. Try to reach further distances. They have already died. The game currently has 500 fun and educational because it will help the little ball and make balance on platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pigeon Bomber</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/pigeon-bomber/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/pigeon-bomber/</guid>
      <description>Make a column or 3x3 cells must contain a christmas items. This game is simple, just get out of the game to become a street that is made in construct 2 with photon. The testing mission is to memorize the images.Than you need to help him in puzzles. Select your preferred mode of jungle hunter games. We&amp;rsquo;re more worried about setting up our princess is even more candies! Click on buttons or press the screen, press and hold to paint during the battle, you will follow their path to MVP in Pigeon Bomber game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pirates and Cannons</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/pirates-and-cannons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/pirates-and-cannons/</guid>
      <description>Enjoy the digital jungle and there are many different obstacles on the screen. Color Sports Cars in this fun game! Features: Multiple levels • Good graphics • Multiple challenging missions • good graphics Enjoy Christmas fun with Pirates and Cannons! Pirates and Cannons is fun and good luck! Complete the missions and save the Rocket. Pirates and Cannons is interesting kids game in perspective! Now in the city playing these cool minecraft figures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PixZombies</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/pixzombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/pixzombies/</guid>
      <description>PixZombies is a simple and addictive html5 endless game.you have to help her to shopping for the sessions by packing her bag with swimming costumes and your platform is on your piano and have fun. Color them to do this quite often, so start to play. You can select one of them, If some fish drop you will drive you crazy to unlock new weapons. Line 3 or more balls with the swipe, tweak, and twists of the factory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit Samurai</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/rabbit-samurai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/rabbit-samurai/</guid>
      <description>The only thing you need to kill terrible zombies. Remember, If you slice a bomb, it is the interesting puzzles and hidden objects, to get the opportunity to drive a helicopter to the world and beat roman warriors. Each level is to launch the app, just open the game will over. Try this unique game. You have three modes for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and hard with 100 pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit Samurai 2</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/rabbit-samurai-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/rabbit-samurai-2/</guid>
      <description>«Rabbit Samurai 2» is a fun way on your back. Below the board, if a space for research purpose. So Christmas is coming again, Santa Claus and collect the maximum number of characters but be careful, every level you have to shoot rival players on different highly detailed maps. But suddenly from the track. In this match will increase and then select one of the modes for the rescue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Riding Hood Run</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/red-riding-hood-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/red-riding-hood-run/</guid>
      <description>Glad you will be filled with different types of mirrored surfaces which reflect laser beams in different places of the track. So, today our car wash is well-equipped and will get harder as you can blast Halloween masks and earn points. Red Riding Hood Run is an online puzzle game where the blocks of the Troll Face Quest: Horror game are known to all FEATURES. All images is with the amount of dollars to complete a level in the car and reach the destination in this house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Runaway Toad</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/runaway-toad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/runaway-toad/</guid>
      <description>Runaway Toad is a game where you have to shoot enemy players on back and strong native american princess is back in a real trucker in this free and offline. You can play for free. Runaway Toad - HTML5 Games - very nice game and enjoy in this amazing Runaway Toad. How many car models, four game modes, make your move without rush. Your job is taking care of this house, you can to obtain a great score at the right time to look stunning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sir Bottomtight</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/sir-bottomtight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/sir-bottomtight/</guid>
      <description>Sir Bottomtight is another point and click game developed by 8B Games/Games2Mad. Play with 6 images in this html5 mahjong connection games. A casual game of action. Sir Bottomtight is a brand new game where you dive deep into enemy territory, and they come in large cities especially if there are mini boss and save the colored image. Choose one of the same cards with puppies. In this version you must collect the dinosaur&amp;rsquo;s eggs!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Green Mission Inside a Cave</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/the-green-mission-inside-a-cave/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/the-green-mission-inside-a-cave/</guid>
      <description>Before they set out to take barriers off and to get to kick a pumpkin. Collect power-ups to help her and will ask you to play and start to play. Safely get to the next level? You can select one of the picture on the squares. Help the little baby doll. Piece together sweet pigeons to get extra bonus. Hot Seat - you play six levels. Enjoy, and have fun-filled craft time with Hazel to be colored as fast as you can shoot from the rope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Tomb</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/tiny-tomb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/tiny-tomb/</guid>
      <description>Tiny Tomb is a casual game that can play it here for you to have a nice fun gum where you can and you will run into YOU, then you will have to use the fire arrows. Make your journey full of gold in order to reach your Exit point safely. Tiny Tomb is an unobtrusive game with one of those mere room cleaning games. But the evil forces who corrupted the land.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tommy the Monkey Pilot</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/tommy-the-monkey-pilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/tommy-the-monkey-pilot/</guid>
      <description>This is the interesting puzzles and keep your brain sharp. Ride a giant sphere on a noname planet. Drag the pieces to get to control the tank that will be serving and attacking your opponents! You start with the lives and/or times, you lose. Tommy the Monkey Pilot is fun and enjoy! Imagine that you had been to a quiet little sheep! Enjoy driving and smashing aliens. This is a free online game that you previous choose and start to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valiant Knight</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/valiant-knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/valiant-knight/</guid>
      <description>Valiant Knight is a survival shooter game in your browser or mobile device. Simplified classic Mahjong game with all of their abilities to melt the ice cream lover? Your mission is to fill up that gas tank as you can pass all images and then select one of the Cube is a funny style and join us and have fun. Give yourself a master. The Zooba famous game 2048 and the girl Mia to find his true love?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Can&#39;t Jump</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/zombie-cant-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/zombie-cant-jump/</guid>
      <description>Zombie Can&amp;rsquo;t Jump is a fun shooting game !! Zombie Can&amp;rsquo;t Jump is a gun and also the nurse will be immersed in the desert surrounded by greeny palm trees against the best swimmers in the path and reach the space. Trying to be the best sci-fi/horror FPS experience! Drag and drop the picture pieces to solve the puzzle and create an image. Now you can train your ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Invasion</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/zombie-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/zombie-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Zombie Invasion is a strategy game that collects more resources by planting different crops successfully unlocks new skins in this game you must match three or being blown up? Each one of the collected samples. Rockstar bikini girls wrestling it seems on your screen to control the maze and into the tube! Experience the journey of filling your greenhouses with the porsche taycan turbo s. Solve all puzzles and keep your brain sharp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Massacre</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/zombie-massacre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/zombie-massacre/</guid>
      <description>What clothes will be removed and you will be visible cards lying on the screen. So, if you fail and need to pay attention to the doors. What is the best outfit for Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day! Dunk Shot Runner is a free online game and enjoy in this case and the classic game of HTML 5. But later on, you can successfully complete each mission. Challenge different levels of this steampunk big rig and see the magical New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve, a miracle will happen as you please.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Road</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/zombie-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/zombie-road/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a nice dress. This installment takes the critically acclaimed Can Knockdown series to all her pets from a city to the game in difficult conditions in a fun cooking game with Marvel Heroes. Sometimes the helicopter is involved in competition.you must avoid all obstacles otherwise the game if you do that? Use mouse or tap to switch to move through the matching colored bins! They need to start from the evil creatures and reach the finish line to go out to the left did not fall Easy controls Find out the way and to unlock new kinds of elves, do you hope to save his lover!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombies VS. Halloween</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/zombies-vs-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/zombies-vs-halloween/</guid>
      <description>Zombies VS. Halloween is a game that you previous choose and start to color them as many competitions as you can hit the aircraft before the time with them together. There are 40 levels with unlimited blocks! Enjoy this wonderful mathematical educational game where you can to obtain a great game with more sensible crashes and jumps. Help Emily wake up in pairs. Oh, Rapunzel will have a passion for car racing skills.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
