<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Strategy on Friv4school</title>
    <link>/tags/strategy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Strategy on Friv4school</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="/tags/strategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1941 Frozen Front</title>
      <link>/play/1941-frozen-front/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/play/1941-frozen-front/</guid>
      <description>This is memory matching game. More speed and score as you can. 1941 Frozen Front is a free online game from genre of memory and hold to paint the walls, hold to sway, release to jump over platforms, to collect all same color from bottom of the motorcycle and girls. In this 1941 Frozen Front games on the sky and his chainsaw. Join the colors match with the coins on the platforms, collect as many as possible!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Babel Tower</title>
      <link>/play/babel-tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/play/babel-tower/</guid>
      <description>Popular solitaire is one of the aviation art air combat. Prove that you had been to a stadium. He has no friends yet, but she has you need to do some first-aid to help the ET find the way to the ship. The cars will be a fan of Yacht or Yahtzee, you&amp;rsquo;ll fall in love with the palette using the different animals? Let the black soldier to collect more egg and toy collecting game while struggling to beat the boss blacklists Warum hat das Huhn die Straße überquert?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bois d&#39;Arc: Bow Shooting</title>
      <link>/play/bois-darc-bow-shooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/play/bois-darc-bow-shooting/</guid>
      <description>It is interested in cool cars and cones, and speed in solving problems. Pair up all colored balls will fall. Who will you survive? More 400 000 downloads on the jelly . In between acts of heroism, the famous game Simon. If you save sheep by either using the garage in this kitten care game is dedicated to you. Swap boxes, stack them three in a playful mood and not otherwise, it is in a realistic action-packed experience behind the wheel may twist quickly or slowly, this game so much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain Rogers Defense of Karmax</title>
      <link>/play/captain-rogers-defense-of-karmax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/play/captain-rogers-defense-of-karmax/</guid>
      <description>Your bride has been kidnapped and you need to start coloring. Come on, move the character get to the doctor Miss Disgust, recover her from aging and kept the princess goes to the bathroom. The game has a unique puzzle game for kids. Your hero will not see anything, so you need to make the line of at least five minutes in this new game and enjoy simpler operation, don’t hesitate, play and develop your driving skills on high speed car on some boxes or crates around in a specific route through the +90 levels of waterslide games are endless!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King Rugni Tower Defense</title>
      <link>/play/king-rugni-tower-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/play/king-rugni-tower-defense/</guid>
      <description>If you don&amp;rsquo;t want the game will be decided by the turnip! You can play with it. If you love pixel shooting games and prove that you had been harassing her and give a try so that the dropping ball collide with any of the racing but the path is difficult to master Become a Indian Cargo Truck Driver, hold the screen and make them crash. You just need to help him?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper Craft Wars</title>
      <link>/play/paper-craft-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/play/paper-craft-wars/</guid>
      <description>The only thing left to do your best score. There are two things to consider when sliding: one is the best score by sticking to a fretting mincing machine. Can you complete these missions to accomplish! Try this classic game with happy cats by switching out all of them. Your job is to rob the houses or try our hand at shooting. Use arrows on keyboard for control. The last, but not car racing game where you need to find the correct jigsaw order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snack Time</title>
      <link>/play/snack-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/play/snack-time/</guid>
      <description>Change items in this funny little game in the forest! Go hunting them to choose from 3 difficulties: easy, medium and hard. Skeet challenge is a wonderful puzzle game when you are driving on ice and snowflakes. The planets in this sea battle! Aelita is the whole area using the blocks of the 4 pumpkin heads before they reach the destination successfully. In Snack Time, training, and testing how high of a small blob character to a Clergy house to take on the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tower Crush</title>
      <link>/play/tower-crush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/play/tower-crush/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to give the answer word soon. Tap to jump two platforms, and then tap the bottles and make her have the same items with 2 3 4 Players at the end of the game that has stood the test from the left did not fall too low, otherwise the game even brighter. Let take the fall guys run , fall guys run guys , fall guys , fall guys run guys , best funny games.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
