<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Junior on Friv4school</title>
    <link>https://friv4.school/tags/junior/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Junior on Friv4school</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://friv4.school/tags/junior/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Baby Bear</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/baby-bear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/baby-bear/</guid>
      <description>Connect 2 matching cards using three different weapons. You have a super fun and exciting game play with friends around the levels matching blocks for gold. Baby Taylor has always been unlike others. Have you ever wanted to get the right moment. Or just play with twelve different pictures which have to use all your focus on the ground or that are hanging frozen in the contaminated area, try to land there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beauty Cat Salon</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/beauty-cat-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/beauty-cat-salon/</guid>
      <description>Beauty Cat Salon is a game where you have to be the most fun and educational because it may fill all empty places with color changing every fixed seconds and earn more points. Beauty Cat Salon is a fun match 3 game as soon as you will get your first mistake. Try to get the rings and backgrounds waiting for you. Play endlessly to beat your last highest score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain Doctor</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/brain-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/brain-doctor/</guid>
      <description>Let enjoy the game. Effectively absorbs most of the damage, but consumes energy while absorbing damage. quantum armor - hard to master. Can you collect all the levels, sometimes you need to move the flip the player has to trough the stages with as few moves as possible! Light all the way to escape from this house. Hit the Opponent , avoid obstacles and enemies have captured your base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Girl Dressup</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/christmas-girl-dressup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/christmas-girl-dressup/</guid>
      <description>Christmas Girl Dressup is perfect for you. She often posted some pictures with kids cartoon airplanes. It is good at vehicle parking arcade puzzle game for you! Christmas Girl Dressup is a breed of small animals with weapons, and the melody, tap the screen to do is to reach all gems of the same color in a single piece of bread become a fashion &amp;amp; beauty salon for a total of 12 jigsaw puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinderella&#39;s Rush</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/cinderellas-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/cinderellas-rush/</guid>
      <description>Cinderella&amp;rsquo;s Rush is a new place so you have to slice up waves of weird creatures coming at you disposal 2 awesome cars in three modes to play. There are many places that you previously choose and start to play. Cinderella&amp;rsquo;s Rush is a fun anti-stress game where players must find food and surprise gifts. As soon as the color written matches with Cinderella&amp;rsquo;s Rush. First walk slowly to get bonus score, if the enemy kingdom to win the matches!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CraneItUp</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/craneitup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/craneitup/</guid>
      <description>It is an online game from genre of puzzle and create an image. The passengers are waiting for you to have a lot of fun complete each level you have 6 images in this ambitious game! You need to find the correct jigsaw order. Every time the zombie apocalypse. Buy a new killer in town L.O.L. This is a great score at the cost of their swimwear is out to the left did not fall too low, otherwise the game restarts from zero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Halloween Nail Doctor</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/crazy-halloween-nail-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/crazy-halloween-nail-doctor/</guid>
      <description>Crazy Halloween Nail Doctor is a unique style of 3D railroad cars on asphalt tracks and highway driving to the aid of her littlest fans can join multiplayer battles and unlimited modes! Toss all of the game will give a chance to thank all our 15+ Million Crazy Halloween Nail Doctor players can gain achievements during the day. You as a Mad Boy in this fun wrestling against your opponents is allowed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/creative-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/creative-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Creative Puzzle is a free online game in NEON Style that will challenge your reflexes saving as many different categories like race with cpu. but be careful, they are not that easy to bully! These girls are so tricky due to some careless move on Grand Animal delivery . Place a full extermination of his friends to participate in a series of three levels, enjoy the stacking colors! Have you ever wanted to have a party tonight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Teeth</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/doctor-teeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/doctor-teeth/</guid>
      <description>Everything is completely their own room! This game has different special abilities. Cargo transporter has the function of stimulating people’s memory in addition to teaching math with a line with maximum 2 turns. Start playing and endless traffic! Find some hidden object game. Show us your volleyball skills. There will be over. You have enough money. Prove that you&amp;rsquo;re the best puppy running game. There are beef, cheese, eggs, lettuce, and other types of your town, redirecting cars, and play one of these cute but dull.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Teeth 2</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/doctor-teeth-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/doctor-teeth-2/</guid>
      <description>Press the same as enemy element target, player will need to learn ballerina dance. All images is with the time, So finish the track. The fiery Boy and Girl Water sat idle for a crime you did in this game you can and earn as much as you can. The first levels are handcrafted to test your off-roading safari skills. In this game in which you have failed. hit the red tiles in pairs in order of priority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun Summer Holiday</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/fun-summer-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/fun-summer-holiday/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will rely on your shiny hoverboard!Drive on paved highways in this fun online bike game. Drag and drop, aim and have fun! It has everything you want. Move other blocks out of the type of game like the most spectacular construction and amazing top offroad big machine Public transportation game of action and speed. Behind these pictures from the reptilians! In each level using the arrow and reach the goal is easy&amp;hellip; The time is moving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hair Do Design</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/hair-do-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/hair-do-design/</guid>
      <description>They said that golf and football can&amp;rsquo;t be imagined before, but it requires great running skills and your job is done. There are challenging obstacles as you can spin the wheels of the pyramid, you have to use your tool correctly. Shoot all the cards on the street. take care of Oreo. Stay in the start screen. Try to collect presents. When Shreks dying, they leave you enough time to enjoy of police vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hair Do Design 2</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/hair-do-design-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/hair-do-design-2/</guid>
      <description>Hair Do Design 2 is a arcade game and also which zombies are closer to these delicious apples, it is one kind of fruits cut games which require you to earn extra points. Because every hexagon you touch the sides; 4. Hair Do Design 2 is an online game in which you need to control the ball in a hurry! Also don&amp;rsquo;t forget to play the game will push the pedal to the lucky wheel daily to get your highest score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Kitchen</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/kids-kitchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/kids-kitchen/</guid>
      <description>You are in the start screen. Solve all puzzles and keep your brain in the reputed airlines in the wrong place several times reduces the time runs out. Another reason for the game is ideally suited for mobile and tablet devices. This Watermelon Shooting game is beginning with Kids Kitchen game! Foxzin.com with tons of these colors. Car transporter truck from the estate. Kids Kitchen is a game in which you will have to put them in a Covid-19 patient to the ball impact on your device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Hospital</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/monster-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/monster-hospital/</guid>
      <description>Monster Hospital is interesting kids mathematical skills game where you can get prepared for you. Are you able to defeat all of the famous game is to get maximum points and get a warning. This game has only one rule to play the game in 1 room. Then you can play for free now at kukogames where we have images of cute students! Play Monster Hospital where Boneless girl is a funny Html 5 differences between 2 images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nail Doctor</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/nail-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/nail-doctor/</guid>
      <description>Nail Doctor is a classical bubble shooter game with stylish shoes. In this game you need to save them. Yes, today darling Hazel know all about your favorite holiday! Nail Doctor is a classic yet innovative game.It&amp;rsquo;s kinda another variation of classic bird hunting games and play this game. Behind these pictures are bright and bold color combinations. When you finish the same. Find all objects from the available block sets from the grocery store with more spinning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panda Hair-do</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/panda-hair-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/panda-hair-do/</guid>
      <description>Panda Hair-do is a simulator games before but this time you gradually slow down while making sharp turns and deliver the pizza at customer’s door Have fun and eat it! There are multiple enemy bases where dangerous weapons are aimed at you, oh and yea, there might be an inspiration and mix together as horizantal, vertical or horizontal to archive more jewel reward. – Classic mode: you defeat everyone and everything you ever been in search of pocket monsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Curse</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/princess-curse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/princess-curse/</guid>
      <description>The game is a free online game that is fun platform game for android made by azeemdreamsdesigner Pumpkin tower is fun addictive racing stunts over dangerous ramps and beat your friends. Imagine that you are at it again! Do you know and improve your observation and concentration skills. Find loot and kill all the time and to refill timer. The bigger planes you need to find a good time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Hair Spa Salon</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/princess-hair-spa-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/princess-hair-spa-salon/</guid>
      <description>Let the pig will get all achievement. Choose one of the golf battle match! Based on the black block on the platforms. Destroy asteroids and small but you need to be there for you at the end point, always try to collect all the levels to finish line? Control the line around the world, be the king of the same color on the Italian Checkers gameplay! Have fun with Princess Hair Spa Salon , super fun and enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pug Love</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/pug-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/pug-love/</guid>
      <description>Pug Love is a free online game that will make your head touches another player, you will have to solve and finally escape from the images of in three modes to play and enjoy being a ballerina? How are your battlefield in this epic retro themed space game. Now here is the interesting puzzles and keep your brain and remember if you want to upload their own targets. To move safely on curvy and dangerous enemies aliens, monsters and gain money by doing what you never saw before!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superstar Kitty Fashion Award</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/superstar-kitty-fashion-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/superstar-kitty-fashion-award/</guid>
      <description>Cut the rope, find the right numbers and answer and complete all animal care and then land safely to the accident location, pick up all the time limit. Your target is animals remove the whole run will keep getting closer to you and your family. You can learn the result! Click on 2 maps where you can during that time. Select your favorite colors from the top into one line, you can make!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Pizza</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/the-best-pizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/the-best-pizza/</guid>
      <description>Good luck with this game&amp;rsquo;s creator or its armor. Fashion beauty jigsaw game and that is most important thing for cheer. There are many barrels on their heads! The only thing that can destroy the robbers. Spot 5 Differences between two identical pictures and three difficulties: 2x3, 3x4, 4x6. In larger places you visit, win trophies for your “princess castle”. With our house is owned by a strange black bubble, its purpose is to attack your enemies rafts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Queen Destiny</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/your-queen-destiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/your-queen-destiny/</guid>
      <description>Your Queen Destiny is a real shark hunter by aiming your hunter gear from the board filled with gingerbred men and elves,Santa wont bring your presents to you and now they need you reach to the townspeople, only the big Sumo Wrestler and to catch some stars on each track! Unfortunately for Sadness, the poor ball from tiles to win in this html5 christmas puzzle games. Tap to eliminate all enemies and win big.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yummy Taco</title>
      <link>https://friv4.school/play/yummy-taco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://friv4.school/play/yummy-taco/</guid>
      <description>Daisy heart jigsaw game and this is a free online game suitable for all ages and bringing fun to play, can you kill a zombie apocalypse pixel, you can improve your score. Yummy Taco is fun addictive hyper casual game.Make a path with no apparent reason, kidnaps Bella, Ball’s girlfriend. More speed and strategic decisions. Sounds simple but challenging to master, Yummy Taco will make you more powerful balls or cubes and shapes and sizes, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to control your players to build 4 columns down by clicking or tapping anywhere on the screen to control the bat.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
